timetotrade.eu 2019-04-03

# Privacy Policy

**TigerWit Limited (“TigerWit”, “we”, “us”, “our”) is subject to data protection legislation in the UK. We are therefore committed to protecting your privacy and maintaining the security of any personal information that we receive from you. If this Policy changes, we will place an updated version on this page.**

The purpose of this policy is to explain to you what personal information we collect and how we and our associated companies may use it. We take client privacy very seriously and train our staff on their privacy obligations. 

**Who we are**

TigerWit Limited is a private limited company registered company in the UK under registration number 09479466, and is authorised and regulated by the FCA under registration number 679941. Our registered address is 7th Floor, Augustine House, 6A Austin Friars, London, EC2N 2HA, United Kingdom. We provide online trading platforms for customers who wish to trade in equities and over the counter products such as CFD’s and Forex.

This Privacy Policy along with the Privacy Notice details how we collect and process personal data, how you can request access to your data, and what you can then do with it or instruct us to do with it.

 **How we obtain your information** We receive or collect personal information about you through your registration and application, and any subsequent emails, letters, telephone calls and conversations made in the course of our relationship with you. In accordance with UK data protection legislation this information is securely stored to prevent unauthorised access.

 **How we check your identity** To comply with money laundering regulations we have a legal obligation to confirm that certain aspects of the information that you have supplied are true and correct. This process is commonly called “Know Your Client” or “KYC” . We will ask you to submit personal information through the application form, and the application process will involve electronic verification of such data via commercially available third party sources, such as a credit reference company. Our search is not seen or used by lenders to assess your ability to obtain credit.

Where we are unable to verify your identity to the standards required by us we may ask you to send us copies/scans of documentation such as a passport or utility bill.

 **Using your information** We may process your information for one or more lawful bases of processing depending on the purpose for which we use your data. For example, we may send you marketing material from time to time by email, telephone, SMS or other electronic messaging services on the basis that you have given us consent or if it is in our legitimate interest to do so. If you do not then wish to receive marketing information from us you will be able to opt out electronically at any time.

Your personal information may be disclosed to:

  * service providers who have been contracted to provide us with IT, financial, administrative, regulatory, compliance, or other services
  * introducing brokers with whom we have a mutual relationship
  * courts, tribunals and regulatory authorities as authorised by law
  * credit reporting or reference agencies
  * anyone authorised by you to receive such information such as Money Manager

Generally we require that external organisations who handle or obtain personal information acknowledge the confidentiality of this information, undertake to respect any individual’s right to privacy, and comply with all the relevant data protection laws applicable to them. Please note that the use of your personal information by external third parties who act as data controllers of your personal information is not covered by this privacy notice and is not subject to our privacy standards and procedures.

We may transfer your personal information outside the European Economic Area to other Tigerwit group companies as well as processors who are engaged on our behalf.

Joint Accounts: Where you have applied for an account with a third party (i.e. a joint account) your information may be visible to those third parties.

 **How we store your personal information and for how long.** We take very seriously the safeguarding and privacy of your personal information, whether you interact with us personally, by phone, by mail, over the internet or any other electronic medium. We hold personal information in a combination of secure computer storage facilities and paper-based files and other records, and take steps to protect the personal information we hold from misuse, loss, unauthorised access, modification or disclosure. 

When we consider that personal information is no longer needed, we will remove any details that will identify you or we will securely destroy the records. However, there are some legal and regulatory obligations that we must adhere to which means that we need to maintain some records for a significant period of time. For example, we are subject to certain anti-money laundering laws which require us to retain copies of the documents we used to comply with our customer due diligence obligations, and supporting evidence and records of transactions with you and your relationship with us for a period of up to seven years after our business relationship with you has ended. Any personal information in the form of a recorded communication, by telephone, electronic, in person or otherwise, will be held in line with local regulatory requirements, currently for up to seven years after our business relationship with you has ended. Where you have opted out of receiving marketing communications we will hold your details on our suppression list so that we know you do not want to receive these communications.

We train our employees who handle personal information to respect the confidentiality of customer information and the privacy of individuals. We regard breaches of your privacy very seriously and will impose appropriate penalties, including dismissal where necessary.

 **If TigerWit Ltd is involved in an acquisition or restructuring, your information may be shared with the acquiring/acquired entity if it is in our legitimate interest to do so or if we are provided to comply with any legal obligation to do so.**

 **Transaction Activity:** your trading activity remains the property of TigerWit Ltd and may be used by us where we have a legitimate interest to do so or to comply with any legal obligations we may have. Where your trading activity is revealed to third parties your actual identity will remain private.

 **Prevention of terrorism and crime** Where we are required by law, your personal information may also be disclosed to an applicable governmental, regulatory or enforcement authority. These authorities may then use your personal information to investigate and act on any breach of law or regulatory rules in accordance with their procedures. Whilst we can advise such authorities as to their privacy obligation we cannot control their use of your data.

 **We record all phone calls** with you in case we need to check we have carried out your instructions correctly, to resolve queries or disputes, for regulatory purposes, to help improve our quality of service, and to help detect or prevent fraud or other crimes. Conversations may also be monitored for staff training purposes.

 **You may obtain a copy of all the personal information that we hold on you by making a Subject Access Request.** Normally we will respond to your request within one month and no fee will apply. However if the request is manifestly unfounded or excessive, or repetitive in its nature, we may either extend the time to respond and/or charge a reasonable fee, or refuse to deal with the request. Your rights in relation to your personal data are outlined in our Privacy Notice.

 **What is a Cookie and how do we use them?** Cookies are small pieces of text stored on your computer or mobile device when you visit a website or app. Cookies help us determine the type of browser and settings you are using, where you have been on the website or in the app, when you return to the website or app, and to ensure your information is secure. The purpose of this information is to provide you with a more relevant and effective experience, including presenting relevant content according to your needs or preferences. We may also use independent external service providers to track the traffic and usage on the website. See our Cookie Policy for more information.

Information on deleting or controlling cookies is available at [www.AboutCookies.org](https://www.aboutcookies.org/).

However you should be aware that you may not be able to access some parts of our site or app if you choose to disable the cookie acceptance in your browser, particularly the secure parts of the site. We therefore recommend you enable cookie acceptance to benefit from all of our services.

If you have any questions or complaints about privacy, please contact our Compliance department at:

The Compliance Department  
Tigerwit Limited  
7th Floor  
Augustine House  
6A Austin Friars  
London  
EC2N 2HA  
UK

If you are not satisfied with our response to a complaint, you have the right to lodge a complaint with our supervisory authority, the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO). You can find details about how to do this on the ICO website at <https://ico.org.uk/concerns/> or by calling their helpline on [0303 123 1113](tel:+443031231113).
